A Guide to the University of Virginia Health System Marketing Communications collection, 1857-2006, bulk 1950-2000
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Series I: Departmental materials, 1907-2002
  - Urology, 1941-2002
    - Portrait of John Henry Neff, first Head of Urology at UVA, and Plaque in honor of William Lott Ainsworth, undated (Box-folder 3:166)
    - Albert J. Paquin, Urology, Chair, undated (Box-folder 3:167)
    - Paul Shin, Urology, undated (Box-folder 3:168)
    - Samuel Vest, Urology, undated (Box-folder 3:169)
    - Hugh Warren, Urology, undated (Box-folder 3:170)
- Series II: Buildings and grounds, circa 1857-2006
  This series contains images of various buildings, facilities, and locations across the UVA Health System and includes historical photographs, negatives, and drawings of UVA buildings, some of which are undated.
  - University Infirmary, circa 1857 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - University Hospital, circa 1901 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - University Hospital west facade, architectural drawing by Paul J. Pelz circa 1904 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - University Hospital with South Wing, 1905 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Operating Theater at UVA Hospital, circa 1913 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Original Martha Jefferson Hospital, circa 1920 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - University Hospital with Steele Wing addition, circa 1920 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Old UVA Medical School, architect's drawing, circa 1926 (Box-folder 4:8)
    Designed by Coolidge, Shepley, Bulfinch, and Abbott
  - Old Medical School just after completion, taken from the roof across the street, 1929 January 22 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Blue Ridge Sanatorium patients and nurses on the roof, circa 1929 (Box-folder 4:10)
    In the online Visual History collection, instances of this image are labeled as the roof top of the Steele Wing in the old University Hospital
  - The Corner, circa 1929 (Box-folder 4:11)
    Includes Chancellor’s drug store
  - Anatomical Hall, and drawings of Anatomical Hall (undated), circa 1920-1930 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Hospital Wards, “Old E Ward”, circa 1920-1930 (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Operating Room, circa 1920-1930 (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Barringer Wing of the University Hospital, Interior view, circa 1930 (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Medical School Laboratory, circa 1920s-1940s (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Hospital buildings exteriors-roofs, 1945 April 13 (Box-folder 4:17)
  - McKim Hall, 1946 (Box-folder 4:18)
  - Davis Ward, University Hospital 1947 (Box-folder 4:19)
  - University of Virginia Gate and (Old) Medical School circa 1947 (Box-folder 4:20)
  - University of Virginia, Medical Center, and Charlottesville, aerial viewscirca 1947 (Box-folder 4:21)
  - Cancer Research Building site: tearing down arcade to make from for the cancer building 1949 August 6 (Box-folder 4:22)
  - Operating Room staff and equipment, 1949 (Box-folder 4:23)
  - Rear of the University Hospital and the School of Medicine, aerial view, circa 1950-1951 (Box-folder 4:24)
  - University Hospital Construction, 1958 February 18-June 25 (Box-folder 4:25)
  - Foundation work for the University Hospital expansion, 1958 July 16 (Box-folder 4:26)
  - University Hospital Multi-story addition aerial view, circa 1960 (Box-folder 4:27)
  - Anatomical Hall model, 1969 (Box-folder 4:28)
    Constructed in 1969 by Ira L. Full for Chalmers L. Gemmill
  - I.T. Transport and Hospital Parking, 1970 May (Box-folder 4:29)
  - Medical Center Storeroom, “J.-J. Storeroom” 1971 February (Box-folder 4:30)
  - New Facilities of the Division of Prosthetics and Orthotics in the Towers, later known as the Jefferson Park Medical Office Building, 1971 May 14 (Box-folder 4:31)
    Pictured: Faulkner, Division of Prosthetics
  - O’Neill Building on Jefferson Park Avenue, Family Practice and Extended Health Care Building, and photographs of the Corner 1971 Winter (Box-folder 4:32)
  - Front view of the University Hospital (West Complex), 1973 (Box-folder 4:33)
  - Medical Center aerial view, 1973 (Box-folder 4:34)
  - Plans for Primary Care Unit, 1974 March 15 (Box-folder 4:35)
  - Emergency Department Staff and Emergency Entrance with Ambulance, 1974 October (Box-folder 4:36)
  - University of Virginia and Medical Center aerial views, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 4:37)
  - University of Virginia and Medical Center aerial views, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 4:38)
  - Blue Ridge Hospital aerial views, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 4:39)
  - Primary Care Center, 1980 (Box-folder 4:40)
  - Health Sciences Library exterior, circa 1980 (Box-folder 4:41)
  - Primary Care Center, Jordan Hall, West Complex, and other images, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 4:42)
  - Health Sciences Library, Historical Collections display cases and book shelves, circa 1981-1982 (Box-folder 4:43)
  - Architect’s renderings of the New University Hospital by Joint Venture Architects, circa 1983-1984 (Box-folder 4:44)
  - Assorted historic negatives, including early University Hospital views, unknown event with Thomas Hunter, nurses, and graduation group, 1984 May (Box-folder 4:45)
    Printing job for John Harland; date likely refers to creation of negatives
  - Architect’s drawing of Ambulatory Surgery Center Front Entrance, 1984 August 27 (Box-folder 4:46)
  - New University Hospital under construction, 1988 June (Box-folder 4:47)
  - New University Hospital under construction, aerial views, circa 1988 July (Box-folder 4:48)
  - New University Hospital under construction, 1988 September (Box-folder 4:49)
  - UVA Medical Center and Helipad, aerial views, 1988 October (Box-folder 4:50)
  - New University Hospital interior views, 1988 December 20 (Box-folder 4:51)
  - West Complex (Old Hospital) with snow, photographed by C.G., 1988 (Box-folder 4:52)
  - Buzz’s Flying Pegasus Helicopter and the New University Hospital, circa 1990 (Box-folder 4:53)
  - New University Hospital interiors, including isolation facilities, circa 1988 (Box-folder 4:54)
  - New University Hospital interiors (before the move), 1989 February 2 (Box-folder 4:55)
  - New University Hospital, exterior and interior (before the move), 1989 February 14 (Box-folder 4:56)
  - New University Hospital, the Lawn, and Mad Bowl aerial views, 1989 April 28 (Box-folder 4:57)
  - Children’s Rehabilitation Center, aerial views, circa 1989 (Box-folder 4:58)
  - New University Hospital interiors (before the move) [PART 1], circa 1989 (Box-folder 4:59)
  - New University Hospital interiors (before the move) [PART 2], circa 1989 (Box-folder 4:60)
  - UVA Medical Center, aerial views, circa 1989 (Box-folder 4:61)
  - UVA Medical Center, aerial views (negatives), circa 1989 (Box-folder 4:62)
  - Pegasus Helicopter and the New University Hospital, 1990 April 9 (Box-folder 4:63)
  - Elson Student Health Center, 1990 (Box-folder 4:64)
  - UVA Medical Center exteriors and interiors, 2006 July 19 (Box-folder 4:65)
  - Blue Ridge Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:66)
  - General George Rogers Clark statue and park, undated (Box-folder 4:67)
  - Jordan Hall, and West Complex negatives, undated (Box-folder 4:68)
  - Jordan Hall entrance, undated (Box-folder 4:69)
  - Madge M. Jones Activity Terrace, 7th floor of University Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:70)
  - The Lawn and Medical School aerial view, undated (Box-folder 4:71)
  - McLeod Hall, undated (Box-folder 4:72)
  - McKim Hall, undated (Box-folder 4:73)
  - Medical Center aerial views with Jordan Hall, Nursing School, West Complex (Old Hospital), and Power Plant, undated (Box-folder 4:74)
  - Medical Center parking garage under construction, undated (Box-folder 4:75)
  - Medical Research Facility, MR-4, architect’s drawing, undated (Box-folder 4:76)
  - Medical School negatives, including Harvey Jordan and aerial views, undated (Box-folder 4:77)
  - Models of Medical Education Building and Jordan Hall with the Health Sciences Library, undated (Box-folder 4:78)
  - Claude Moore Rehabilitation Center, artist’s rendering, undated (Box-folder 4:79)
  - New University Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:80)
  - New University Hospital, artist’s rendering by ? McIntosh, undated (Box-folder 4:81)
  - New University Hospital floor plans, undated (Box-folder 4:82)
  - New University Hospital, Jordan Hall, and Health Sciences Library, undated (Box-folder 4:83)
  - New University Hospital, Pegasus, and unidentified researcher (photographs from Marketing brochures), undated (Box-folder 4:84)
  - Night prints of the New University Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:85)
  - Old UVA Medical School, undated (Box-folder 4:86)
  - Old UVA Medical School, undated (Box-folder 4:87)
  - Old UVA Medical School, etching by Don Swann, and reference photographs, undated (Box-folder 4:88)
  - Old UVA Medical School exterior and interiors, undated (Box-folder 4:89)
  - Pavilion V on the Lawn, artist's rendering, undated (Box-folder 4:90)
  - Pavilion VIII on the Lawn, Residence of Harvey Jordan, undated (Box-folder 4:91)
  - Power Plant at the Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:92)
  - Satellite Centers: Augusta Medical Center, Augusta Pediatrics, Blue Ridge Pediatrics, Cardiac Health and Fitness Center, Child and Family Psychiatry, Craigsville Family Medicine, Crossroads Family Practice, Middlebrook Family Practice, McCue Center, Northridge, Orange Medical Center, Pediatric Association of Waynesboro, Stoney Creek Family Practice, and University Physicians at JABAundated (Box-folder 4:93)
  - West Complex and Barringer Wing entrances to the Old Hospital, undated (Box-folder 4:94)
  - West Complex (Old Hospital), undated (Box-folder 4:95)
  - West Complex (Old Hospital), Jordan Hall, and Nursing School, aerial viewsundated (Box-folder 4:96)
- Series III: Events and people, circa 1873-2006
  This series contains images documenting UVA Health System events, staff, and students. It includes a group of portraits featuring UVA Health System faculty and administrators.
  The records are arranged into sub-series according to subject matter. Items in each subseries are arranged chronologically.
  - Events, circa 1984-2006
    - Health Sciences Library groundbreaking, with Wilhelm Moll, 1973 July (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Groundbreaking, possibly Health Sciences Library with unidentified individual, 1973 August (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for the New University Hospital, circa 1984 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Check Passing Ceremony with William H. Muller, 1986 March 25 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Check Passing Ceremony with Dr. William Muller, The Merck Company Foundation, 1987 March 12 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Week of the Nurse with Beth White, at McKim Auditorium, 1987 July 28-30 (Box-folder 5:6)
    - William H. Muller’s Retirement Party, 1987 September 30 (Box-folder 5:7)
    - Employee of the Month with Dr. John T. Ashley, University Hospital Executive Director1988 October 6 (Box-folder 5:8)
    - James S. Kennan with donor, gift of a car at Blue Ridge Hospital, 1989 February 14 (Box-folder 5:9)
    - Employee Awards Banquet with Don Detmer, 1989 (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Employee Awards Banquet, negatives, 1989 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Employee of the Month, Dr. Ely, 1990 March 1 (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Tour of the 7th Floor Pediatrics area, including the Madge M. Jones Activity Terrace, at the new University Hospital, and Rotunda Dinner event, 1990 September 21 (Box-folder 5:13)
    - Richard F. Edlich receiving the Jefferson Award, with Robert Carey, Don Detmer, and Senator Robb, 1990 October 6 (Box-folder 5:14)
    - Check Passing Ceremony with Dr. Hugh Kelly, 1990 October 22 (Box-folder 5:15)
    - Check Passing Ceremony for the Virginia Power Newborn Nursery, with Don Detmer (on left), 1990 October 26 (Box-folder 5:16)
    - John Harlan’s Retirement Party, 1990 December 14 (Box-folder 5:17)
    - Employee Awards Banquet, with Linda Coiner, 1990 (Box-folder 5:18)
    - Nursing School Pinning Ceremony, 1990 (Box-folder 5:19)
    - Kid Safe Day, 1991 March 23 (Box-folder 5:20)
    - Mobil Check Passing Ceremony, 1991 April 19 (Box-folder 5:21)
    - Employee Appreciation Picnic, 1991 May 15 (Box-folder 5:22)
    - Nursing School Pinning Ceremony and Graduation, 1991 May 18-19 (Box-folder 5:23)
    - UVA General and Medical School Graduation Exercises, with Edward W. Pullen (Anatomy) and Robert Carey, 1991 May 19 (Box-folder 5:24)
    - Check Passing Ceremony for Madge Jones donation, 1991 June 12 (Box-folder 5:25)
    - Health Sciences Library 15th Anniversary Celebration, with Don Detmer, Linda Watson, Donald Lindberg (Director of the National Library of Medicine), and photographs of library facilities and technology, 1991 (Box-folder 5:26)
    - May Day Party, with Gary Holdren, 1991 (Box-folder 5:27)
    - School of Medicine Graduation Exercises, 1992 May 17 (Box-folder 5:28)
      Negatives
    - Presentation of the Lamar R. Plunkett Award, 1992 June 28 (Box-folder 5:29)
    - Dr. McLean’s Retirement Party, with Francis Coffey at the Pavilion VI garden 1992 August 22 (Box-folder 5:30)
    - Cancer Benefit Concert with Mary Chapin Carpenter, Debbie Ryan, and Emily Couric, at Old Cabell Hall Auditorium 2001 May 11-12 (Box-folder 5:31)
    - Buck v. Bell Historical Marker Unveiling, with Paul Lombardo (marker sponsor), Joan E. Klein, Jesse Meadows, Rose Brooks, and Historical Collections staff, 2002 May 2 (Box-folder 5:32)
    - Helen French Award Presentation: Virginia House joint resolution honors Ms. French for the MERCI Program, 2003 April (Box-folder 5:33)
      Left to right: Ed Howell, Delegate Mitch Vaneers, Helen French, and Leonard W. Sandridge; Image used in The Link
    - Leadership Kick-off meeting, with Ed Howell, 2006 February 1 (Box-folder 5:34)
    - Academy of Distinguished Educators Awards Presentation at the General Faculty Meeting held in the Old Medical School Auditorium, 2006 September 7 (Box-folder 5:35)
    - Check Passing Ceremony with Frank T. Saulsbury of Amoco Oil, undated (Box-folder 5:36)
    - Groundbreaking with Mark Jones, undated (Box-folder 5:37)
  - Portraits, undated
    - Early Faculty Portraits: John P. Emmet (Natural History), Robert Empie Rogers (Chemistry), Charles Slaughter? (Physiology), J. Lawrence Smith (Chemistry), William Towles, (Anatomy), undated (Box-folder 5:38)
    - Portrait of John F. Anderson, undated (Box-folder 5:39)
      Hung in the Dean’s Office during the tenures of Kenneth Crispell and Edwin Pullen
    - Portrait of Paul B. Barringer, undated (Box-folder 5:40)
    - Portrait of Sydney Britton?, Physiology, by David Silvette?, undated (Box-folder 5:41)
    - Portrait of James Cabell, Professor of Anatomy, Physiology, and Surgery (1837-1889), undated (Box-folder 5:42)
    - Portrait of James Edgar Chancellor, undated (Box-folder 5:43)
    - Portraits of Robley Dunglison, undated (Box-folder 5:44)
    - Portrait of William H. Goodwin, undated (Box-folder 5:45)
    - Portrait of Bryd Leavell, Internal Medicine, undated (Box-folder 5:46)
    - Portrait of Edwin Partridge Lehman, undated (Box-folder 5:47)
    - Portrait of Edwin Partridge Lehman, undated (Box-folder 5:48)
    - Portrait of Thomas Hugh Nelson, Dr., M.D., undated (Box-folder 5:49)
      Photographed by Holsinger studio
    - Portrait of Stephen H. Watts, undated (Box-folder 5:50)
  - School of Medicine Students, circa 1873-1994
    - Medical School Class of 1873 in front of Anatomical hall with James F. Harrison, James L. Cabell, and John B. Minor, professors, circa 1873 (Box-folder 5:51)
    - Medical School Class of 1876-1877 with Paul Barringer, circa 1876-1877 (Box-folder 5:52)
    - Class of 1935 First Year and Fourth Year Class Portraits, with Byrd Leavell, 1931-1935 (Box-folder 5:53)
    - Third Year Class (Class of 1944), School of Medicine, 1943 (Box-folder 5:54)
    - Reunion of the Medical School Class of 1935, with Bryd Leavell1960 June (Box-folder 5:55)
    - Fourth Year Class Portraits (Class of 1962), School of Medicine, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 5:56)
      Item (11.5 in x 15 in) stored with oversize materials in the Historical Collections Photographs Room.
    - Nursing? Students, Marsha W? 1986 (Box-folder 5:57)
    - Class of 1989 Individual Student Portraits, School of Medicine, 1987 (Box-folder 5:58)
      Also includes student listings for SOM class of 1988 and SOM class of 1990
    - First Year Class (Class of 1990), School of Medicine, 1987 (Box-folder 5:59)
    - Fourth Year Class (Class of 1987), School of Medicine, 1987 (Box-folder 5:60)
    - Second Year Class (Class of 1989), School of Medicine, 1987 (Box-folder 5:61)
    - Third Year Class (Class of 1988), School of Medicine, 1987, 5:62
    - First Year Class (Class of 1993), School of Medicine, 1989 (Box-folder 5:63)
      Contains composite portraits and negatives
    - First Year Class (Class of 1993), School of Medicine, 1989 (Box-folder 5:64)
      Includes negatives and lists of names
    - Class of 1991 Individual Student Portraits, School of Medicine, circa 1991 (Box-folder 5:65)
    - First Year Class (Class of 1996), School of Medicine, 1993 (Box-folder 5:66)
    - Second Year Class (Class of 1995), School of Medicine, 1993 (Box-folder 5:67)
    - First Year Class (Class of 1997), School of Medicine, 1994 (Box-folder 5:68)
      Composite portraits
    - Spinal Chords at a Children’s Miracle Network Telethon (School of Medicine students), undated (Box-folder 5:69)
  - UVA Health System affiliates (identity or affiliation uncertain), circa 1917-2002
    - World War I Base Hospital No. 41 members, circa 1917 (Box-folder 5:70)
      UVA-sponsored medical unit in WWI
    - Assorted Photographs for the Physicians Directory, 1982 (Box-folder 5:71)
      Includes Stanton P. Nolan, Morton C. Wilhelm, Brian R. Williamson; Photographed by Marianne Sullivan
    - UVA Hospital? Advisory Board, 1986 December (Box-folder 5:72)
    - Flora Green Workshop, 1987 June 15 (Box-folder 5:73)
    - Sara Fry, 1987 June (Box-folder 5:74)
    - George King, 1991 February 28 (Box-folder 5:75)
    - Unidentified Medical Center staff, 1996 September 19 and undated (Box-folder 5:76)
      Photographed by Dan Grogan, UVA staff photographer, and Jackson Smith
    - Assorted Photographs for the Physicians Directory, 2000 February 25 (Box-folder 5:77)
      Includes Ivan Crosby, Surgery; ? Sarbin
    - Tabara?, 2001 September 7 (Box-folder 5:78)
    - Nikko? Mayo, 2001 September (Box-folder 5:79)
    - Unknown physician, circa 2001 (Box-folder 5:80)
    - Mary Beth Bellah, CCS?, 2002 (Box-folder 5:81)
    - Chaplain Service, undated (Box-folder 5:82)
    - Clinical Lab photographs, undated (Box-folder 5:83)
      Individuals identified as Mr. Melon and Scott
    - Don Detmer (?) and an unidentified person, undated (Box-folder 5:84)
    - ? Gonzalez, undated (Box-folder 5:85)
    - Steven Kron, undated (Box-folder 5:86)
    - Dr. McManus ?, undated (Box-folder 5:87)
    - Medical Center staff photographs (miscellaneous), undated (Box-folder 5:88)
      Lee Thompson, Christopher Williams, Joe Whelan, Karen Schwenzer, Anthony May, Edward Ullan, Janet Martin, Aviv Benmeir, John Densmore, Randal Blank, David Calfee, Noreen Crain, Dennis Templeton, Ronald Turner, Elizabeth Rice, Kathryn Kerkering, Roger Burket, Devin Brown, Tomasz Oron, Evan Heald, Yam Gera, Sona Tabbara, Michelle Barr, Michael Vock, some unidentified
    - Miscellaneous Health System personnel photographs, undated (Box-folder 5:89)
    - Mike Nelson, Ex-football player, undated (Box-folder 5:90)
    - Kristen Plehn, undated (Box-folder 5:91)
    - ? Webb, undated (Box-folder 5:92)
    - ? Worrall, undated (Box-folder 5:93)
    - Unidentified negatives, undated (Box-folder 5:94)
    - Unidentified photographs, undated (Box-folder 5:95)
- Series IV: Marketing publications and related materials, 1981-2004
  This series contains images, drafts, image CDs, editing notes, and consent forms related to UVA Health System published materials, including Helix, Health Talk, and others.
  - Helix Volume 16 Number 1 Spring 1999, 1999 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Helix Volume 17 Number 2 Summer 2000, 2000 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Helix Volume 17 Number 3 Fall 2000, 2000 (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Helix Volume 18 Number 1 Winter 2001, 2001 (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Helix Volume 18 Number 2 Spring 2001, 2001 (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Helix Volume 18 Number 3 Fall 2001, 2001 (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Helix Volume 18 Number 3 Fall 2001, Editor's notes and correspondence, 2001 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Helix Volume 19 Number 1, Winter 2002, 2001 (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Helix Volume 19 Number 2, Summer 2002, 2002 (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Helix Volume 19 Number 3, Winter 2003, 2002 (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Helix Volume 19 Number 4, Spring 2003, 2003 (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Health Talk Winter 2002 photographs, 2002 (Box-folder 6:12)
    Includes Bruce G. Bateman, Joseph Whelan, and Christopher Williams (Obstetrics and Gynecology)
  - Health Talk Spring/Summer 2002 photographs, 2002 (Box-folder 6:13)
    Includes Ruth Ralston (Pediatrics RN), Jennifer Harvey (Radiology)
  - Health Talk Spring 2003 photographs, 2003 (Box-folder 6:14)
    Includes Carlos D. Ayers (IM) and Mark A. Russell (Dermatology)
  - Health Talk Summer 2004 photographs from Telethon article, 2004 (Box-folder 6:15)
    Photographed Jeff Lindholm?
  - Health Talk Winter 2004 slides, 2004 (Box-folder 6:16)
    Photographed Jackson Smith
  - Patient Information Brochure photographs and comments by Robert Blizzard and others, 1981 (Box-folder 6:17)
  - Biomedical Communications MSC photographs, circa 1980s (Box-folder 6:18)
  - Marketing stock photographs of John T. Ashley, UVA Hospital, and Blue Ridge Hospital, circa 1980s (Box-folder 6:19)
  - Marketing and Communications assorted negatives, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 6:20)
  - Urology Department brochure, 1997 February (Box-folder 6:21)
  - Photographs of UVA Hospital Marketing materials, including banners and signs, 1997 Spring (Box-folder 6:22)
  - Digestive Health Center brochure, 2000 March (Box-folder 6:23)
  - Digestive Health Center brochure, 2000 July (Box-folder 6:24)
  - Otolaryngology Patient Guide, 2001 January (Box-folder 6:25)
  - University of Virginia Hospital Centennial brochure, 2001 January, 6:26
  - Pediatric Emergency Room Brochure, 2001 July (Box-folder 6:27)
  - Fertility Services advertisement for Albemarle Magazine, 2002 March (Box-folder 6:28)
  - Media Services surgery photograph shoot, 2003 (Box-folder 6:29)
  - Directional road map for Charlottesville area, undated (Box-folder 6:30)
  - UVA Hospital Hospitality House Seal, undated (Box-folder 6:31)
- Series V: Unprocessed materials
  This series contains 4 records boxes of unprocessed slides, image CDs, and zip disks.
  Access to this series is restricted.